

## Jin (Hyeong) Park, MS

Research Engineer at AI Research Institute, Neowiz | Seoul, Republic of Korea Email: jhpark.4745@gmail.com | Webpage | Linkedin

### **SUMMARY**

An AI research engineer in the game industry, keen to impress audiences through computer graphics combined with machine learning. Jin's best capabilities cover the signal processing, geometry processing, and data-driven approaches. His work has been contributing to the growing game development industry in South Korea, notably by working on one of the first AAA game titles (Lies of P) solely developed from the Korean game industry.

\*2023 Game of the Year (Apple Store Awards & NYX Game Awards)

\*2024 Apple Design Awards: Visuals and Graphics

Research Interests: Inverse Rendering, Accelerating Physically-Based Rendering, Neural Material Representation

#### **EDUCATION**

Chung-Ang University (CAU), Seoul, Korea

Mar 2018 - Mar 2020

M.S. in Computer Science and Engineering (Focus: Machine Learning)

• Advisor: <u>Jaesung Lee</u> | GPA 3.82/4.0

Thesis: Effective Front-end Architecture Search for Random Weight Network on Edge Device

Korea National University of Transportation (KNUT), Gyeonggi-do, Korea

Mar 2014 - Mar 2018

B.S. in Computer Science and Information Engineering

• Advisor: Sungwook Lee | GPA 3.67/4.0

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### AI Research Institute, Neowiz | Head: Sung-Gyu Oh

Dec 2020 - Present

Research Engineer

- Leading the development of the AI portion of a 2023 Game of the Year Nominated AAA game title (Lies of P)
- Currently applying deep learning solutions to generate resources for game development, including SFX, 3D meshes, and 3D animations.
- Developed and introduced a AI-based semantic search system to retrieve AAA game resources efficiently; specific to SFX and Graphic resource
- Implemented deep learning in the Game content difficulty prediction QC process, leading to a 30% reduction in operational costs (DJMAX)

## Machine Intelligence Lab, Chung-Ang University (CAU) | PI: Dr. Jaesung Lee

Research Assistant Research Intern Mar 2018 - Aug 2020

Jul 2017 - Feb 2018

#### \* 2 lead authored & 2 co-authored works

- Publication Works #1 (co-authored): Multi-label Naïve Bayes Classifier Considering Label Dependence; data preprocessing, experimental design and studies, statistical analysis, manuscript writing, and minor revision support
- Publication Works #2 (co-authored): Implemented a compact feature subset for music categorization on mobile devices; performed data analysis, conducted experiments, and provided technical support throughout the research process.
- **Publication Works #3 (lead authored)**: Multi Population Memetic Search for Effective Multi-label Feature Selection
- **Publication Works #4 (lead authored)**: Evolutionary Algorithm Design for Effective Multi-label Feature Selection

• Mentored experimental design and academic paper writing for junior MS student and undergraduate interns

### **INDUSTRY PROJECTS**

# **Automated Hair Guide Model Generation for Game Characters** from 3D Reconstruction

Apr 2024 - Present

Neowiz, South Korea

**Keyword:** 3D Content Generation, Inverse Rendering, Geometry Processing

- Designed a hair guide model generation pipeline to optimize the creation of game hair models, utilizing Geometry Processing techniques including clustering, importance sampling, and resampling.
- Developed a post-processing procedure that parametrically differentiates guide hair using results from existing Inverse Rendering research.

## **Enhanced Game Image Generation AI Service Development and Feature Integration**

Jan 2024 - Present

Neowiz, South Korea

**Keyword:** Stable Diffusion-based Image Generation, ComfyUI, Human-Computer Interaction

- Developed and enhanced the AI service for game artwork by integrating features including concept art generation from sketches, specific art style application, and diverse background variations from prompts.
- Successfully implemented these advanced functionalities into the live service, improving the creative workflow and expanding the game art production capacity

## **Preliminary Research on Motion In-Betweening for 3D Character Animation**

Sep 2023 - Dec 2023

Neowiz, South Korea

Keyword: 3D Animation Interpolation, Conditional Motion Generation, Data-driven Approach

- Explored the real-time generation feasibility of intermediate motions for in game animation in new AAA game titles
- Implemented a prototype about other published works on the Unreal Engine and conducted real-time performance evaluation

## Quality Control in Rhythm Games through Automated Difficulty Level Evaluation

Jan 2023 - Present

Neowiz, South Korea

Keyword: Deep Learning, Regression Analysis, Active Learning, Content Design Support Tool

- Automated the difficulty level evaluation for new contents in rhythm games (DJMAX) using deep learning
- The automation model achieved a 30% time costs reduction for QC process

#### **Semantic Search System Development for Effective Game Resource Retrieval**

Nov 2022 - Dec 2023

Neowiz, South Korea

**Keyword: General-Purpose Representation**, Vector Search, Elasticsearch, 3D Assets, SFX

- Established the semantic search system based on similarity using general-purpose audio representations generated via SSL
- Implemented an Iterative Search mechanism to refine searches according to user intention; achieved higher semantic results accuracy
- Improved search performance significantly on over-300K SFX files database; enhanced resource retrieval efficiency

## Development of Facial Animation Pipeline for Lip Sync and Emotion

Aug 2022 - Oct 2022

based on Voice and Script [video]

Neowiz, South Korea

**Keyword: Facial Animation**, Sentiment Analysis, Production Design Support Tool (Blender)

- Developed an automated pipeline for facial animations in cartoon-style games
- Constructed the pipeline utilizing a Script-based Sentiment Analysis Model and Speech2Viseme Model to automate the facial animation creation

**Neural Audio Filter for Transforming Monster Voices into Machinery Sounds** [video] Jun 2021 - Oct 2022 *Neowiz, South Korea* 

Keyword: Digital Signal Processing, Audio Style Transfer, GANs, Audio Super-Resolution

- Conducted research on style domain transfer to convert monster voice into machinery sounds while preserving the original nuances
- The output of this research was utilized as SFX in a AAA games (Lies of P), which won the Game of the Year awards at the 2023 Apple App Store Awards and NYX Game Awards

## **Development of ClickML - An Internal AutoML Desktop Application**

Dec 2020 - May 2021

Neowiz, South Korea

Keyword: AutoML, Tabular Data, Time Series Data, Classification, Prediction, Cross-Platform Development

- Developed AutoML App implementing various ML algorithms (XGBoost, Naive Bayes, AR, etc) to handle both tabular and time series data for classification and prediction tasks.
- Successfully ported the application across Windows, Linux, and MacOS, enhancing the accessibility and
  efficiency of machine learning model building within the organization, significantly reducing data analysis
  and model deployment time.

## ACADEMIC PROJECTS

## Korean Music Reproducing System based on Cultural Aesthetics

Mar 2019 - Mar 2020

Ministry of Science and ICT, South Korea

**Keyword:** Digital Signal Processing, Audio Style Transfer, Generative Adversarial Networks (GAN)

• Developed a GAN-based music reproducing system using digital signal processing to transfer traditional Korean musical styles to contemporary music, enhancing cultural appreciation.

## Development of Computer based Three-Dimensional Medical Image Analysis Program for the Objective Assessment of Orbital Disease

Sep 2018 - Oct 2019

National Research Foundation of Korea

**Keyword:** Computer Vision, 3D Deep Learning

- Conducted the research project for thyroid orbitopathy classification in medical CT images using 3D Convolution-base Neural Networks
- Achieved a performance of 1) 97% on binary classification tasks and 2) 92% on multi-classes classification tasks, as measured by the ROC curve

## Post-human era, Build HAI(Humanities with Artificial-Intelligence) for enhancing

Jun 2018 - Aug 2020

the humanity value

Ministry of Education, South Korea

Keyword: Natural Language Processing, Ancient Literature Data, Statistical Analysis

## **Inter-cultural Korean Music Discovery based on Pluralistic Music Emotion**

Mar 2018 - Aug 2018

Ministry of Future Creation and Science, South Korea

Keyword: Digital Signal Processing, Neural Network, Music Recommendation System

• Developed a music recommendation system by generating a joint embedding space for emotions and music features using digital signal processing and neural networks.

#### **PUBLICATIONS AND PRESENTATIONS**

#### **Published in SCI(E) Journals:**

Hae Cheon Kim, <u>Jin-Hyeong Park</u>, Dae Won Kim, and Jaesung Lee, "Multi-label Naïve Bayes Classifier Considering Label Dependence", *Pattern Recognition Letters*, Vol. 136(1) 279-285, **2020** 

Jaesung Lee, Wangduk Seo, <u>Jin-Hyeong Park</u>, and Dae Won Kim, "Compact Feature Subset Based Multi-label Music Categorization for Mobile Devices", *Multimedia Tools and Applications*, Vol. 78 4869-4883, **2018** 

#### **International Conference Presentation:**

<u>Jin-Hyeong Park</u>, and Jaesung Lee, "Multi Population Memetic Search for Effective Multi-label Feature Selection" 2019 International Conference on Platform Technology and Service, Boo Young Hotel & Resort, Jeju, South Korea, (2019)

#### **Korean Conference Presentation:**

<u>Jin-Hyeong Park</u>, and Jaesung Lee, "Evolutionary Algorithm Design for Effective Multi-label Feature Selection" Spring Conference of SEBS & KISM, 1(1):241-242, CAU 100th Anniversary Memorial Hall, Seoul, South Korea, (2018)

## ADDITIONAL PROJECTS

### **Ray Tracing Implementation**

Dec 2023

- Implemented a basic ray tracing engine from scratch following the concepts in "Ray Tracing in One Weekend."
- Developed features such as sphere rendering, shading, reflections, and camera control, enhancing understanding of computer graphics and rendering techniques.

### **NeRF Implementation and Key Research Review**

Feb 2024

• Reviewed key research papers on NeRF, summarizing the core techniques and advancements, to deepen understanding of 3D scene reconstruction and rendering methods.

#### AWARDS AND HONORS

#### **Funding & Scholarships**

#### Research Assistantship (A), CAU

Mar 2018 - Mar 2020

• Full Tuition Scholarship

#### National Science & Technology Excellence Undergraduate Scholarship, KSF

Sep 2016 - Jun 2017

• Full Tuition Scholarship

#### Academic Excellence Scholarship, KNUT

Sep 2014 - Nov 2015

Full Tuition Scholarship

#### **Awards**

## Bronze Medal in Featured Code Competition - CommonLit Readability Prize, Kaggle

2021

CommonLit, Inc.

- Text data Readability Level prediction challenge in Kaggle
- Top 10%, [link]

## Silver Medal in Research Prediction Competition - Ion Switching, Kaggle

2020

University of Liverpool

- Time series biological data prediction challenge in Kaggle
- Top 4%, [link]

## **Excellence Award in Software Competition, KNUT**

2017

KNUT Computer Science & Information Engineering Academic Festival

• Developed a Speech Recognition-based smart mirror system utilizing National Public Data

#### Gold Award in Transportation · Convergence · General Challenge, KNUT

2016

Developed an efficient train seat monitoring App about Korea Railroad Corporation

#### TEACHING EXPERIENCE

#### Teaching Mentor for Undergraduate Interns, CAU

Sep 2018 - Mar 2020

• Mentored experimental design and academic paper composition

## Teaching Assistant, CAU

Mar 2019 - May 2019

Artificial Intelligence Class

• Held weekly Q&A Sessions & support undergraduate students mentoring

#### Teaching Assistant, CAU

Sep 2018 - Oct 2018

Numerical Analysis Class

Teaching Assistant, CAU

Mar 2018 - May 2018

Discrete Mathematics Class

#### **LANGUAGE**

• English: Proficient or Advanced

• Korean: Native

#### **SKILLS**

#### **Qualitative Methodologies**

Ethnographic Research · User Interview · Content Analysis · Case Study · Iterative Design and Feedback Loops · Collaboration and Communication

#### **Quantitative Methodologies**

Statistical Analysis • Experimental Design • Signal Processing • Geometry Processing • Data Processing

## **Programming**

Languages: Python • C++ • LaTeX • Javascript Framework: PyTorch • DirectX 11 • Vue.js

Software: Blender • COLMAP • Unreal Engine • Unity • Mitsuba 3 • ComfyUI

#### **MEMBERSHIP**

BrainKorea(BK)21 Four (Associate membership in the Institute for Innovation and Coexistence Education Research, supported by the Ministry of Education and the National Research Foundation of Korea)

#### **EXTRA EXPERIENCE**

- Korean Military Service Completed
- Lab Manager for 2 years (2018-2019), managed primary lab operations and coordinating research activities at the Machine Intelligence Lab, CAU
- Student Representative for the junior year (2016), followed by the senior (2017), Computer Science and Information Engineering Department, KNUT